(Raj:)Hey, you know that beautiful actress...
(Raj:)...who plays the Borg Queen
in First Contact?
(Howard:)- Yeah.
- Well, I just met her gynecologist.
- What are you doing here?
- Fighting for our friendship.
(Sheldon:)As peculiar and annoying as you can be,
you're still my little buddy.
(Sheldon:)I'm not going to let that
end here tonight.
(Sheldon:)Now put down that drink,
Iet's meet Brent Spiner and go home.
(Leonard:)Hey, Sheldon,
I'm so glad you made it.
(Wil:)I found something
I think you might like.
(Sheldon:)What I'd like is for him
to have a more depressing home.
This is quite Iovely.
(Wil:)This is for you.
(Sheldon:)An original mint-in-package
Wesley Crusher action figure.
(Wil:)I remembered your story about
the time you went to a convention...
(Wil:)...to get one signed and I didn't show.
Look at what I wrote.
"To Sheldon, sorry this took so long.
Your friend, Wil Wheaton."